https://www.choosecherries.com/terms-and-privacy/

Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting www.choosecherries.com, a website owned by the Cherry Marketing Institute (CMI). This privacy policy statement tells you how we collect information from you on this site and how we use it.
Information Collected by This Site
Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. As part of the operation of our site, we gather certain types of information about our users, and we would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how to correct or change the information.
We collect two types of personally identifying information from users: personal data (such as names and e-mail addresses); and aggregated data (such as information about traffic patterns on the site, for example how many users log into the site on a daily basis).
Personal Data
Personal data is collected when only users provide personal data to the site, for example in registering for electronic newsletters or other membership services, answering surveys, purchasing items from the site, sending email to the site, and registering for contests and other promotional opportunities.
Aggregated Information
Aggregated information, such as which pages users access or visit and information volunteered by users, such as survey information and/or site registrations, is collected through various methods. For example, we collect IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that “serve up” Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from a website, its servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to the site. We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration and to provide aggregate data to advertisers about the volume of use on the site.
Use of Cookies
Our site also uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write into your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow a website to measure activity on their site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various member-only parts of the site without re-registering. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except for personal information voluntarily provided by you (i.e. during membership registration or a contest), we do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, and that information is not shared with third parties.
Use of Information Collected by Our Site
Our site uses both the personal and aggregated information collected for multiple purposes. The information is used to improve the content of the site, to customize the content and/or layout of the site for each individual user and to notify users about updates to the site or promotional offers or opportunities that we believe will be of interest to you.
Personal information collected by this site may be shared with other Sponsor-owned or controlled entities. With your permission, we may also share personal information collected on the site with prescreened third parties for marketing or promotional purposes. We will provide users with an opportunity to decline this service when such information is requested from you online. In addition, in the event we plan to post any such information on the site (for example, if you are the winner of a contest) we will either notify you of this possibility when you provide the information and/or, if possible, when the information is posted. Personal information may also be shared only as necessary with third parties who provide technical services to the Site, or host portions of the site, who will not share or otherwise disseminate this information other than as necessary to perform these services.
Children and Privacy
We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. At various places on the sites, we ask whether users are under the age of 18, or 13, for example when requesting personal information from a user, we may ask for parental consent. We rely on users to be truthful in responding to these questions.
Individuals Under 13
In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we urge children and adolescents to check with their parents before entering information on our forms. No information should be submitted to or posted on the site by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. The site does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source collected from users under the age of 13 to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection. Users under the age of 13 are asked not to participate in contests or other promotional opportunities, and the site does not knowingly collect information from users under the age of 13.
Individuals 13 Through 17
We request that children under the age of 18 do not submit or post information to the site without a parent or guardian’s consent. The site may collect information, including personally identifying information, from users between the ages of 13 and 17, and this information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by the site and which may be shared with prescreened third parties, with the permission of the user. A user or their parent or guardian may stop the use – either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online as described above in “Use of Information Collected by The Site.”
Links to Other Sites
It is important to note that this site contains links to other sites, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as our site. For instance, if you click on some links on the site, this will take you away from the site and to an entirely different site. This can include links from advertisers, content providers and partners who may use the sites’ logo and or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect data and make uses of it that the sites would not.
USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICY.
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting a revised privacy policy.
—
Non-Discrimination Statement
In accordance with Federal law and U.S. Department of Agriculture policy, this institution is prohibited from discrimination on the basis of race, color, national origin, sex, age, religion, or disability.
To file a complaint of discrimination, write USDA, Director, Office of Civil Rights, Room 326-W, Whitten Building, 1400 Independence Ave, SW, Washington DC 20250-9410 or call (202) 720-5964 (voice and TDD).
USDA is an equal opportunity provider and employer.
Social
Like Us on Facebook
Follow Us on Twitter
Follow Us on Pinterest
Follow Us on YouTube
Tart on Trend
For Media
School Lunch Toolkit
Find us on...
Like Us on Facebook
Follow Us on Instagram
Follow Us on Twitter
Follow Us on Pinterest
Follow Us on YouTube
About Montmorency
Contact Us
Tart Cherry Industry
Terms & Privacy
©Copyright 2020 Cherry Industry Administrative Board. All rights reserved.
This website uses cookies.
We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services.OkNo ThanksPrivacy policy
You Are Now Leaving choosecherries.com
You are about to leave choosecherries.com, and be directed to a third-party website that is not associated with Montmorency Tart Cherries. The link has been provided solely as a convenience to you. Choose Cherries assumes no responsibility for the accuracy, quality, safety or nature of the content on the linked site. Click Continue to visit the requested site, or Cancel to remain on the current page.
Continue
Cancel
